BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 8074, 1996-2009 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2009
- 8075, 1994-2006 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  4/1994 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2006
- 8076, 1993-2006 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  6/1993 - 6/1997; 6/1997 - 7/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2006
- 8077, 1996-2009 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  4/1996 - 4/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 4/2009
- 8078, 1993-2007 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  1/1993 - 12/1997; 1/1998 - 12/2002; 1/2003 - 12/2007
- 8079, 1996-2004 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  4/1996 - 4/1999; 4/1999 - 4/2004
- 8080, 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 5/2005
- 8081, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  11/1995
- 8082, 1989-2007 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 6/1995; 6/1999; 7/1995 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 6/2004 - 7/2007
- 8083, 1995-2004 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004
- 8085, 1999-2005 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  5/1999 - 5/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2005
- 8086, 1991-2009 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2000 - 4/2004; 5/2006 - 4/2009
- 8087, 1991-2009 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- 8088, 1993-2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  10/1993 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 7/2001; 8/2001 - 7/2004
- 8089, 1997-2006 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2006
- 8091, 1996-2006 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  8/1996 - 7/2001; 9/2001 - 7/2006
- 8092, 1988-2006 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  1/1988 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 8/1995; 7/1992 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2002 (MOV); 7/1998 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8093, 1996-2004 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  5/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2004
- 8094, 1996-2008 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8095, 1996-2003 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003
- 8100, 1996-2006 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  7/1996; 7/1999; 7/1999 - 7/2003; 4/2004 - 7/2006
- 8102, 1995-2004 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  5/1995 - 5/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2003; 5/2003 - 10/2004
- 8103, 1994-2003 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  9/1994 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2003
- 8104, 1996-2007 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2007
- 8105, 1994-2003 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- 8106, 1995-2006 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  5/1995 - 5/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8107, 1995-2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- 8108, 1986-2006 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  6/1986 - 5/1989; 6/1989 - 5/1991 (XTN); 6/1991 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8109, 1994-2005 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  8/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2005 (MOA)
- 8110, 1994-2006 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  1/1994 - 11/1996; 12/1996 - 11/1998; 12/1998 - 11/2000; 12/2000 - 2/2001 (XTN- Wages Only); 12/2000 - 11/2002; 11/2002 - 11/2003 (XTN); 12/2003 - 11/2006
- 8111, 1996-2001 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  6/1996 - 5/1998; 8/1998 - 5/2001
- 8112, 1995-2007 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  6/1995 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8113, 1995-2006 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  6/1995 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8114, 1993-2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  1/1993 - 1/1996; 1/1996 - 12/1999; 1/2000 - 12/2004
- 8115, 1993-2003 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  7/1993 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2003
- 8116, 1995-2006 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8117, 1996-2006 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  6/1996 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2006
- 8118, 1993-2001 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  5/1993 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2009 (MOA and AGMT)
- 8119, 1996-2007 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  11/1996 - 11/1999; 11/1999 - 11/2003; 3/2004 - 2/2007
- 8122, 1993-2008 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  4/1993 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005; 4/2005 - 3/2008
- 8123, 1988-2005 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1998; 4/1998 - 3/2001; 4/2001 - 3/2005
- 8124, 1994-2004 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2004
- 8125, 1993-2005 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 3/1997 - 3/2000; 3/2000 - 3/2005
- 8126, 1996-2005 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 8127, 1998-2008 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  5/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2003; 5/2003 - 5/2008
- 8128, 1985-2008 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  4/1985 - 3/1988; 4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2008
- 8129, 1994-2003 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2003
- 8133, 1995-2006 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  9/1995 - 9/1998; 10/1998 - 9/2003; 10/2003 - 9/2006
- 8134, 1997-2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  3/1997; 12/1999; 12/2002; 12/2002 - 12/2005
- 8135, 1996-2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  3/1996 - 11/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2005
- 8136, 2001-2006 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  7/2001; 10/2000 - 7/2006
- 8137, 2002-2007 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  2/2002; 10/2000 - 2/2007
- 8238, 1996-2007 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8139, 1992-2006 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  7/1992 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2002 (MOA); 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8140, 1996-2003 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  6/1996 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2000; 1/2001 - 12/2003
- 8141, 1994-2001 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  8/1994 - 8/1996; 9/1996 - 12/1996; 1/1997 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/1998; 8/1998 - 8/2000; 8/2000 - 9/2001
- 8142, 1998-2006 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  8/1998; 1/1/2002 - 12/31/2006
- 8143, 1992-2006 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  9/1992 - 8/1995; 9/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2006; 7/2003 - 6/2006
- 8144, 1993-2008 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  8/1993 - 7/1997; 8/1997 - 7/2000; 8/2000 - 7/2003; 8/2003 - 7/2008
- 8145, 1993-2007 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  5/1993 - 5/1996; 5/1996 - 5/1999; 5/1999 - 5/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2007
- 8146, 1996-2007 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2007
- 8147, 1995-2006 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  5/1995 - 4/1998 (Local 210); 4/1996 - 3/1999; 5/1998 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2006
- 8150, 1993-2006 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  6/1993 - 5/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2001; 5/2001 - 5/2006
- 8151, 1990-2008 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1998 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2008
- 8153, 1997-2005 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2005
- 8154, 1996-2005 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8155, 1994-2005 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  9/1994 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 9/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2003; 9/2003 - 8/2005
- 8156, 1994-2007 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  6/1994 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2007
- 8157, 1997-2004 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  1/1997 - 8/2001; 9/2001 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2004
- 8158, 1997-2003 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  1/1997 - 12/1997; 1/1998 - 12/2000; 1/1999 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2003 (XTN)
- 8160, 1988-2006 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2006
- 8160, 1988-2006 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- 8161, 1988-2006 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- 8162, 1996-2004 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  5/1996 - 4/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 1/1999 - 12/1999; 1/2000 - 12/2000; 7/2000 - 6/2004
- 8163, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8164, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2006
- 8165, 1996-2006 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  7/1996 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2006
- 8166, 1994-2006 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  10/1994 - 10/1997; 10/1997 - 10/2000; 11/2000 - 11/2003; 11/2003 - 11/2006
- 8167, 1996-2005 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8168, 1995-2009 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  5/1995 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 5/2009
- 8169, 1995-2006 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2006
- 8170, 1995-2006 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- 8171, 1995-2009 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  5/1995 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2009
- 8172, 1995-2006 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2006
- 8173, 1995-2006 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- 8174, 1992-2004 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  6/1992 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2001; 6/1997 - 5/2004
- 8175, 1987-2006 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  7/1987 - 6/1990; 7/1996 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8176, 1995-2006 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- 8177, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  6/1997 - 6/2000; 6/2000 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8178, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- 8179, 1995-2004 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  6/1995 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/1997 - 5/2001; 6/201 - 5/2004
- 8181, 1997-2004 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2004
- 8186, 1997-2005 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8187, 1995-2004 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  6/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2004
- 8188, 1996-2008 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2004; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8189, 1995-2005 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  6/1995 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8182, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  5/2003 - 4/2006
- 8184, 1994-2007 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2007
- 8185, 1991-2007 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002 (MOA); 4/2002 - 3/2007
- 8191, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- 8192, 1996-2008 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005; 7/2005 - 6/2008
- 8193, 1996-2005 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8196, 1996-2006 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  7/1996 - 6/2001; 7/201 - 6/2006
- 8197, 1994-2006 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  6/1994 - 5/1998; 6/1997 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2006
- 8198, 1998-2005 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  6/1998 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2005
- 8199, 1996-2005 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  7/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8200, 1993-2006 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  5/1993 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998 (XTN); 5/1995 - 4/2001 (XTN); 5/2001 - 4/2006 (MOA)
- 8204, 1998-2004 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- 8207, 1996-2006 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  10/1996; 12/2000; 5/2001 - 5/2006; Joslin, IL
- 8208, 1994-2006 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  8/1994 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 9/2002; 10/2002 - 9/2006
- 8209, 1999-2003 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  8/1999; 8/2003
- 8212, 1997-2006 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  5/1997 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2006
- 8213, 1995-2005 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  4/1995 - 8/1995; 9/1995 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/1999; 9/1999 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2005
- 8216, 1992-2007 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  8/1992 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2007
- 8217, 1991-2006 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  4/1991 - 4/1995; 4/1995 - 3/2000; 3/2006
- 8219, 1996-2005 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8221, 1993-2005 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  5/1993 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 6/2001 - 4/2005
- 8223, 1994-2007 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2007
- 8224, 1994-2007 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2001 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2007
- 8225, 1997-2006 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  4/1997 - 5/2001; 5/2001 - 5/2006
- 8226, 1999-2004 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- 8227, 2000-2007 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 4/2007
- 8228, 1998-2004 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8230, 1999-2004 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  12/1999 - 11/2002; 12/2002 - 11/2004
- 8231, 2000-2008 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  4/2000 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2008
- 8233, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  4/2002 - 3/2006
- 8234, 2001-2008 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  6/2001 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2008
- 8312, 2001-2007 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  6/2001 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2007
- 8313, 1988-2006 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  2/1988 - 2/1993; 12/1993 - 8/1998; 1/1998 - 12/2002; 1/1/2002 - 12/31/2006
- 8314, 1996-2009 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  9/1996; 9/2002; 9/2009
- 8316, 2001-2007 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8317, 2001-2008 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  5/2001 - 4/2005; 4/2005 - 4/2008
- 8320, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  7/2007
- 8323, 1998-2007 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  4/1998 - 3/2001; 4/2001 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2007
- 8324, 2002-2006 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  6/2002 - 5/2006
- 8327, 1999-2005 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  5/1999 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2005
- 8329, 1999-2006 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  7/1999 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8330, 2000-2004 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  6/2000 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8332, 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8334, 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  4/2003 - 3/2007
- 8336, 2004-2008 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  2/2004; 3/8/2004 - 2/25/2008
- 8337, 1985-2005 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  9/1985; 2/1988; 10/1993; 2/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 2/2002 - 2/2005
- 8338, 2004-2010 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  1/2004 - 1/2010
- 8340, 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8341, 1996-2002 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  7/1996 - 6/2002
- 8342, 2001-2004 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8343, 2002-2008 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  7/2002 - 6/2005; 7/2005 - 6/2008
- 8344, 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- 8345, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  11/2005
- 8346, 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8347, 1999-2005 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005 (MOA)
- 8348, 1998-2008 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  7/1998 - 6/2008
- 8349, 1998-2008 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  7/1998 - 6/2003; 7/2001 - 6/2008
- 8395, 1999-2005 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  6/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005 (XTN)
- 8396, 1999-2002 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  7/1999 - 6/2002
- 8397, 1998-2004 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- 8398, 2000-2003 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  6/2000 - 6/2003
- 8399, 1997-2007 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2007
- 8400, 1997-2006 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2006
- 8401, 1992-2006 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  7/1992 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8402, 1997-2006 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  7/1997 - 6/2000; 7/2000 - 6/2003; 7/2003 - 6/2006
- 8403, 1997-2006 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- 8404, 1997-2008 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2008
- 8405, 1995-2004 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- 8406, 1989-2007 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1992 - 6/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2002; 6/1997 - 5/2003 (XTN); 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8408, 1997-2007 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- 8410, 1997-2005 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  10/1997 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 8/2005
- 8411, 1997-2006 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- 8412, 1994-2006 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  7/1994 - 7/1996; 7/1996 - 7/1998; 7/1998 - 7/2000; 7/2000 - 7/2003; 7/2003 - 7/2006
- 8413, 1998-2004 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- 8414, 1991-2007 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  6/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2007
- 8415, 1992-2009 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  5/1992 - 4/1995; 3/1995 - 3/1999; 3/1999 - 3/2004; 3/2004 - 3/2009
- 8416, 1992-2006 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  6/1992 - 5/1994; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 6/2000; 6/2000 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8417, 1992-2004 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  8/1992 - 6/1995; 6/1997 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004
- 8421, 1988-2006 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  4/1988 - 3/1990; 4/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1995; 4/1995 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2006
- 8422, 1989-2007 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  4/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 4/2004 - 4/2007
- 8423, 1989-2007 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8424, 1986-2007 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  5/1986 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8426, 2001-2006 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  3/2001 - 3/2003; 7/2003 - 7/2006
- 8427, 1988-2004 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  7/1988 - 6/1991; 8/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004
- 8428, 1989-2007 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1992 - 6/1993; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/1997 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8429, 1988-2005 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 7/1993 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8430, 1996-2010 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2010
- 8431, 1988-2006 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  3/1988 - 3/1991; 3/1991 - 3/1994; 3/1994 - 3/1997; 3/1997 - 3/2000; 3/2000 - 3/2003; 3/2003 - 3/2006
- 8432, 1986-2006 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  6/1986 - 5/1989; 6/1988 - 5/1991 (XTN); 6/1991 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8433, 1990-2004 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1995; 6/1996 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2004
- 8434, 1988-2008 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  6/1988 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8437, 1992-2005 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  5/1992 - 4/1993; 5/1993 - 4/1996; 5/1996 - 4/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8438, 1988-2005 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1992; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2005
- 8439, 1991-2007 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  5/1991 - 4/1992; 5/1993 - 4/1996; 5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8441, 1990-2007 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2007
- 8446, 1992-2007 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  9/1992 - 5/1996; 7/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2003 (MOV); 6/2003 - 5/2004 (MOV); 6/2004 - 5/2007
- 8447, 1988-2011 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2006 - 5/2011
- 8448, 1996-2006 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8455, 1987-2005 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  6/1987 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1994; 6/1994 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2005
- 8457, 1999-2006 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2006
- 8458, 1994-2009 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  5/1994 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2006; 5/2006 - 4/2009
- 8459, 1999-2005 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 8460, 1988-2006 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  6/1988 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8467, 1989-2006 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  6/1989 - 6/1992; 6/1993 - 6/1997; 6/1997 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2006
- 8468, 1989-2006 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  6/1989 - 6/1993; 6/1993 - 6/1996; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 6/1998 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2006
- 8470, 1988-2007 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2007
- 8473, 1989-2008 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 8474, 1999-2007 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  3/1999 - 4/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2007
- 8475, 1999-2005 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- 8476, 1999-2005 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- 8477, 1986-2004 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  5/1986 - 4/1988; 5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2004
- 8478, 1999-2007 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  6/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2007
- 8479, 1995-2003 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  6/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2003
- 8480, 1997-2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  1997-2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 5/2003 - 6/2006
- 8482, 1988-2008 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1991 - 5/1994; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2008
- 8483, 1990-2005 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  5/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 8484, 1987-2008 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  6/1987 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8485, 1990-2004 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  6/1990 - 6/1993; 6/1993 - 6/1996; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2004
- 8486, 1987-2005 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  6/1987 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 8487, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  6/2000 - 4/2005
- 8488, 1996-2005 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- 8490, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  10/2000 - 9/2005
- 8492, 1987-2008 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  6/1987 - 5/1990; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8493, 1989-2004 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  10/1989 - 9/1992; 10/1994 - 9/1997; 10/1997 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 9/2004
- 8494, 1990-2008 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  1/1990 - 1/1993; 1/1993 - 1/1996; 1/1996 - 1/2000; 1/2000 - 1/2004; 1/2005 - 1/2008
- 8495, 1986-2006 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  2/1986 - 3/1989; 4/1989 - 3/1992; 8/1994 - 3/1998; 3/1998 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2006
- 8496, 1986-2006 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- 8497, 1989-2004 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  7/1989 - 7/1992; 7/1992 - 7/1995; 7/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/2001; 9/2001 - 8/2004
- 8498, 1984-2003 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  12/1984 - 10/1988' 11/1989 - 10/1992; 11/1992 - 10/1995; 11/1995 - 10/1997; 11/1997 - 10/2000; 11/2000 - 7/2003
- 8500, 1987-2005 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- 8505, 1998-2008 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  7/1998 - 6/2003; 7/1998 - 6/2008 (XTN)
- 8506, 1990-2005 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8507, 1991-2006 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  9/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8508, 1997-2004 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  9/1997 - 8/1999; 9/1999 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2001; 9/2001 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2004
- 8509, 1995-2006 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  6/1995 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2006
- 8510, 1997-2005 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2005
- 8511, 1991-2007 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  6/1991 - 6/1994; 6/1994 - 6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/2000; 7/2000 - 6/2004; 7/2005 - 6/2007
- 8512, 1992-2007 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  6/1992 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2007
- 8514, 1992-2006 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  5/1992 - 4/1996; 5/1996 - 4/2001; 9/2001 - 7/2006
- 8515, 1990-2005 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 4/2005
- 8517, 1990-2005 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- 8519, 1997-2004 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  6/1997 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2004 (XTN)
- 8520, 1997-2002 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  7/1997 - 6/2002
- 8521, 1997-2006 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  6/1997 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8522, 1995-2005 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  3/1995 - 2/2000; 3/2000 - 2/2005
- 8523, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  10/2000 - 9/2003
- 8524, 1989-2004 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2003; 7/2003 - 5/2004
- 8527, 1997-2003 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  7/1997 - 6/2000; 7/2000 - 6/2003
- 8528, 1992-2004 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  6/1992 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2004
- 8529, 1997-2006 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- 8530, 1994-2003 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- 8531, 1995-2004 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  8/1995 - 8/1998; 8/1998 - 8/2001; 8/2001 - 8/2004
- 8532, 1989-2005 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/19999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8533, 1995-2004 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- 8534, 1995-2004 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 6/2001 - 4/2004
- 8535, 1991-2005 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  6/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1997 - 5/1999; 7/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8526, 1996-2004 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  6/1996 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8537, 1995-2004 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  6/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 5/2001 - 5/2004
- 8538, 1997-2005 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- 8542, 1989-2006 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  6/1989 - 6/1993; 6/1992 - 6/1997; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2006
- 8543, 1988-2009 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  12/1988 - 6/1993; 3/1992 - 6/1997; 6/1997 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2005; 6/2005 - 6/2009
- 8545, 1990-2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  6/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8547, 1990-2006 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  6/1990 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8548, 1999-2006 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  6/1999 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2006
- 8551, 1991-2004 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2004 (XTN)
- 8553, 1992-2006 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1997 (XTN); 8/1997 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2000 (MOA); 9/2000 - 6/2003; 9/2003 - 8/2006
- 8554, 1988-2004 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  5/1988 - 4/1990 (LU 2 and 13); 5/1990 - 4/1994 (LU 2 and 13); 5/1995 - 4/1997 (LU4); 5/1997 - 4/1998 (LU4); 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8556, 1996-2005 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005 (XTN)
- 8558, 1989-2006 (Box 63, Folder 9)